What is machine learning?
什么是机器学习？
You probably use it dozens of times
a day without even knowing it.
您可能会使用它数十次
甚至不知道的一天。
Each time you do a web search on Google or
Bing, that works so well
每次您在 Google 或
Bing，效果很好
because their machine learning software
has figured out how to rank what pages.
因为他们的机器学习软件
已经弄清楚如何对哪些页面进行排名。
When Facebook or Apple's photo application
recognizes your friends in your pictures,
当 Facebook 或 Apple 的照片应用程序
认出你照片中的朋友，
that's also machine learning.
这也是机器学习。
Each time you read your email and
每次您阅读电子邮件并
a spam filter saves you from having
to wade through tons of spam, again,
垃圾邮件过滤器可以帮助您避免
再次费力地浏览大量垃圾邮件，
that's because your computer has learned
to distinguish spam from non-spam email.
那是因为你的电脑已经学会了
区分垃圾邮件和非垃圾邮件。
So, that's machine learning.
这就是机器学习。
There's a science of getting computers to
learn without being explicitly programmed.
让计算机成为一门科学
无需明确编程即可学习。
One of the research projects that I'm
working on is getting robots to tidy
我正在进行的研究项目之一
致力于让机器人打扫卫生
up the house.
上房子。
How do you go about doing that?
你打算怎样做呢？
Well what you can do is have the robot
watch you demonstrate the task and
那么你能做的就是拥有机器人
观看您演示任务并
learn from that.
从中学习。
The robot can then watch what objects
you pick up and where to put them and
然后机器人可以观察什么物体
你拿起它们并将它们放在哪里
try to do the same thing
even when you aren't there.
尝试做同样的事情
即使你不在场。
For me, one of the reasons I'm
excited about this is the AI, or
对我来说，我的原因之一
对此感到兴奋的是人工智能，或者
artificial intelligence problem.
人工智能问题。
Building truly intelligent machines,
构建真正的智能机器，
we can do just about anything that you or
I can do.
我们可以做任何您或
我能做到。
Many scientists think the best way to
make progress on this is through learning
许多科学家认为最好的方法是
通过学习才能取得进步
algorithms called neural networks,
which mimic how the human brain works, and
称为神经网络的算法，
模仿人类大脑的工作方式，并且
I'll teach you about that, too.
我也会教你这一点。
In this class,
you learn about machine learning and
在这堂课上，
你了解机器学习并且
get to implement them yourself.
自己去实施它们。
I hope you sign up on our website and
join us.
我希望您在我们的网站上注册并
加入我们。